MAYANK KASHYAP

www.mayankkashyap.com | PRODUCT MANAGER



+91 - 9716448141



mayankkashyap95@gmail.com

Work Experience

July 2017 - Present

Associate Consultant, User Experience - Microsoft Services

Discover / Design / Build / Test

My role here is to deliver solutions which are accessible to each and every individual and have been developed using industry standard processes starting from discovery to test.

June 2016 - August 2016

Front End Developer - Adurcup

Javascript / HTML CSS / Materialize

Worked on the new ecommerce platform of Adurcup which was aimed to bring their traditional and new customers online.

June 2015 - August 2015

Technical Intern - iLabs Co

Ruby / Bootstrap / Rails Framework

Competify India: Worked end to end on prototype website using ruby on rails framework in a team of two developers.

Key Projects

June 2017

BuildCV.online

Discover / Design / Build / Test

Aimed at reducing the pain of designing a resume, this portal provided users ability to develop their resume in 3 simple steps.

January 2018 - Present

User Experience Consultant - Tetra Pak AB

Discover / Design / Build / Test

Working on IoT Management Tool, a web based solution to manage and control IoT devices remotely, as a part of Smart Factory Project.

October 2017 - December 2017

UI Developer - Petroleum & Explosives Safety Org, GOI Build / Test

Worked on a web based solution for tracing the manufacturing and sale of explosives in India.

Education

2017

B.Tech Computer Science & Engineering

Maharaja Surajmal Institiue of Technology Aggregate: 79.6%

Positions of Responsibilities

2016

Chairperson - Computer Society - IEEE MSIT Student Branch Chief Organizer - Avensis 2016 - Annual TechFest of MSIT

2015

Designer - Avensis 2015 - Annual TechFest of MSIT

About Me

Highly motivated individual, ready to take up new challenges and learn from them in a fun and easy way.

Nationality: Indian Location: Hyderabad Languages: English, Hindi,

Gujarati

Strengths: Hardworking,

Positivity

Weakness: Overenthusiasm
DOB: 19th August 1995

© Process

Discover

Competitive Analysis
Personas & Segmentation
User Research & User Stories
Journey & Flow Mapping
Customer Interviews
Feature Definition
Requirements Gathering

Design

Wireframing
Adobe xD
Balsamiq
Adobe Photoshop
Low & High Fidelity Mockups
MS Powerpoint

Build

Functional Prototyping

HTML • CSS • JavaScript
TypeScript • Angular • Sass •
KnockoutJS • Gulp • Bootstrap

Ruby • Python • Ruby on Rails ASP.Net

REST APIs Wordpress • MS Sharepoint GIT • TFS

Test / Measure

Automation Testing Unit/Contract Testing Selenium • Jasmine.js

Google Analytics User Feedback